A Guide to the John K. Martin Records, 1777-1907
Library of Virginia
- Pension Files, 1777-1883 and n.d., 10.62 cubic feet. (Boxes 1-24)
  - War of 1812, 1812-1883 and n.d., 6.525 cubic feet. (Boxes 6-20)
    - War of 1812 - Peck-Pemberton (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Pegram, Baker, 1853 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Pegram, Henry D., 1852-1859 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Pelter, Peter, 1871-1872 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Pemberton, John, 1878-1879 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - War of 1812 - Pendleton-Peterson (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Pendleton, Edmund, 1852 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Perdue, Batholomew, 1851-1852 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Perrin, Park, 1878 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Perry, John, 1855 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Perry, Reuben, 1856, 1877 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Peterson, Charles, 1855-1857 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - War of 1812 - Pettus-Pitts, James (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Pettus, Hugh M., 1864 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Phillips, William H., 1832 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Phillips, Wesley, 1872-1873 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Pierce, William B., 1857-1858 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Pitt, James, 1854-1860 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - War of 1812 - Pitts-Preston (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Pitts, Thomas H., 1851 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Poe, John, 1856 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Powell, Jonathan, 1851-1852 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Powell, Joshua, 1852-1853 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Powell, William, 1855, 1879 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Prentice, John Brooks, 1871 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Preston, Stephen, 1880 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - War of 1812 - Price-Purdie (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Price, George, 1855 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Priest, Jeremiah, 1856 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Pryor, Brazure Williams, 1852-1854 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Pumphrey, Armistead, 1856 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Purdie, John, 1857 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - War of 1812 - Rachel-Radliff (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Rachel, Alexander, 1829, 1867-1882 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Radliff, John, 1852, 1858 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - War of 1812 - Raines-Raymond (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Raines, Fielding, 1878-1880 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Ramey, Daniel G., 1871 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Raney, Thomas H., 1871 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Rattray, David, 1851-1852 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Ravens, Richard, 1854 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Raymond, G. V. W., 1878 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - War of 1812 - Redford-Richardson, John (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Redford, Francis William, 1852-1858 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Redford, Robert, 1855-1856 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Rennolds, James, 1854 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Reynolds, Reuben, 1852 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Richard, James, 1877-1879 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Richardson, A. T., 1852-1853 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Richardson, John, 1882 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - War of 1812 - Richardson, Lindsey-Rideout (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Richardson, Lindsey 1851-1852 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Richardson, Thomas R., 1878 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Richardson, William, 1881 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Rideous, Benjamin, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Rideout, David, 1855 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Rideout, William, 1855 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - War of 1812 - Riggins-Robertson (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Riggins, William, 1855-1856 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Rison, John, 1857 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Ritchie, John, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Ritter, William, 1853 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Roberts, Thomas, 1857 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Robertson, Joseph R., 1855 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Robertson, William H., 1855-1878 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Robertson, William H., 1878-1880 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Robertson, [_] 1860 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - War of 1812 - Robinson-Rowlett (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Robinson, Alexander, 1861 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Robinson, Campbell, 1854-1855 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Robinson, David, 1878 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Roper, George, 1856-1858 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Rose, Henry, 1853-1854 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Rouzee, Richard, 1852-1856 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Rowlett, Thomas, 1853 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - War of 1812 - Roy-Rucks (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Roy, McCarty D. 1852 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Royal, John, 1857-1858 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Royall, William, 1855 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Royster, Francis W., 1851-1854 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Royster, James H., 1852-1854 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Royster, John W., 1855-1856 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Rucks, Jarvis, 1858 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - War of 1812 - Rudd-Ryan (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Rudd, John A., 1852 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Russell, Jesse, 1879 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Russell, Robert, 1871 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Ryan, Dabney, 1878-1881 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - War of 1812 - Sadler-Sanderson (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Sadler, William, 1852 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Salle, Anderson, 1852, 1878 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Sampson, William, 1879-1880 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Sanderson, Robert, 1858, 1878-1881 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - War of 1812 - Sanderson-Saunders, William (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Sanderson, Robert, 1858-1859 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Saul, Hiram, Jr., 1856 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Saul, Hiram, Sr., 1851-1855 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Saunders, John H., 1878 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Saunders, Williams, 1880-1881 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Saunders, Williams, 1881-1882 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - War of 1812 - Saunders, Williams-Scott (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Saunders, Williams, 1882 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Savage, Allen, 1855-1857 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Scott, Robert G., 1846-1856 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Scott, Thomas, 1879-1880 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Scott, Thomas, 1880-1881 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - War of 1812 - Seal-Sharpe (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Seal, James, 1853-1859 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Seammel, John, 1877 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Seay, Austin, 1880 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Seddon, John, 1851 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Senot, Leonard, 1857-1858 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Sharp, Nelson, 1858 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Sharpe, Price, 1852 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - War of 1812 - Shaw-Sherman (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Shaw, Thomas, 1854 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Sheffield, Pleasant, 1852 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Sheffield, Stephen, 1858 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Shepherd, Anderson, 1855-1858 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Sheppard, Peter, 1855 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Shepperson, William, 1850 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Sherman, William M., 1857 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - War of 1812 - Shifflett-Thompson (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Shifflett, John, 1879 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Shipnash, Michael, 1879 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Shirley, William O., 1859 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Simms, John, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Simpkins, Robert, 1854-1855 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Simpson, John, 1882 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Sims, Chapman, 1857-1858 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Sims, John, 1872 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - War of 1812 - Sipple-Smith, Richard L. (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Sipple, Henry, 1879 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Smart, Moses, 1853 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Smith, Granville, 1854 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Smith, Hezekiah, 1867 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Smith, John, 1879 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Smith, Peter, 1856 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Smith, Richard L., n.d. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - War of 1812 - Smith, Theodore (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Smith, Theodore R., 1853 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Smith, Thomas, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Smith, William B., 1851 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Smithers, Edmund, 1875-1876 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Smithers, John, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - War of 1812 - Snyder-Spencer, Thomas J. (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Snyder, William, 1878 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Somers, Jacob, 1880 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Spann, Zephaniah, 1861 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Speed, John, 1878 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Spencer, Nathan, 1856 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Spencer, Thomas F., 1878-1879 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Spencer, Thomas J., 1878-1879 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - War of 1812 - Spencer, Urias-Stamper (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Spencer, Urias, 1853-1854 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Spencer, [_], 1852 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Spicknall, William, 1855 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Spires, Frederick, 1856-1860 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Spriggs, Robert, 1858 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Spronce, John, 1853 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Stamper, James, 1880 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - War of 1812 - Staunton-Stone, Edmund (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Staunton, Elihu, 1851-1859 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Staunton, Elihu, 1859-1861 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Steel, John, 1855 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Stegall, Richard, 1855 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Sterling, Samuel H., 1851-1853 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Stith, Obediah, 1855 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Stokes, Brooking, 1854 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Stone, Edmund, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - War of 1812 - Stone, John B.-Sullivan, Daniel V. (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Stone, John B., 1882 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Stradford, Mathew, 1857-1858 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Sullivan, Claiborne Derrett 1852-1857 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Sullivan, Daniel V., 1879-1880 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - War of 1812 - Sullivan, Frances B.-Talley (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Sullivan, Frances B., 1871-1877 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Sullivan, Frances B., 1878 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Sumner, Owen, 1880 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Talbot, Edward, 1832, 1857 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Talley, John, 1877-1878 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - War of 1812 - Talley-Tally (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Talley, Joseph, 1878-1879 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Talley, Parks, 1855 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Talley, William, February-April 1881 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Talley, William, May-June 1881 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Tally, James, 1853 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - War of 1812 - Tarrant-Terrell (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Tarrant, Richard, 1854 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Taurman, William, 1855 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Taylor, Edmund B., 1858 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Taylor, Mathew, 1859-1861 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Taylor, Nathaniel, 1874-1878 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Tenser, Andrew, 1853 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Tenser, Leopold, 1854 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Terrell, John, 1872 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - War of 1812 - Terry-Thomson, Randolph (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Terry, William, 1878-1879 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Thacker, Chesley, 1872-1873 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Tharp, Richard, 1853 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Thomas, James, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Thomas, William, 1851, 1872 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Thompson, Henry, 1853 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Thompson, Roger, 1852 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Thompson, Randolph, 1880 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - War of 1812 - Thompson, Thomas-Thurston (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Thompson, Thomas J., 1853 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Throgmorton, Reuben, 1853 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Thurman, Hezekiah, 1853, 1860 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Thurmond, Elisha, 1857 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Thurston, Francis, 1861 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - War of 1812 - Tibbs-Tinsley (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Tibbs, James T., 1850, 1852 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Tice, M., 1880 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Tindall, John, 1874 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Tingler, Jacob, 1879-1880 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Tinsley, Bennett, 1855, 1858 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - War of 1812 - Tinsley-Toothman (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Tinsley, Nathaniel, 1856 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Tisdale, William, 1857 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Todd, R., 1878 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Todd, Thomas, 1859 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Toler, William I., 1854 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Toothman, John, 1879 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - War of 1812 - Towell-Tucker, James (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Towell, John F., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Towler, John, 1851 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Tribble, George, 1853 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Trimmer, James W., 1818, 1854-1855 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Trueman, Jacob, 1855 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Tucker, Berryman, 1874, 1878 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Tucker, James, 1852-1855 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - War of 1812 - Tucker, John-Tyree (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Tucker, John 1849, 1857 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Tucker, Joseph, 1855 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Turpin, Henry, 1879 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Tyler, Seaton, 1851, 1878-1879 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Tyree, John, 1851-1852 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - War of 1812 - Vaden-Vest, James (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Vaden, Isham W., 1852 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Valentine, James, 1851 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Vaughan, Pleasant, 1882 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Vaughan, Vincent, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Vaughan, William, 1850 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Vaughan, William W., 1855 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Vaughn, Henry, 1850 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Vest, James, 1853 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - War of 1812 - Vest, Philip-Walker, Charles (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Vest, Philip, 1855 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Via, Gillson, 1878 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Viglini, Joseph, 1852 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Wade, Robert, 1853 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Walden, John B., 1853-1857 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Waldrop, Richard, 1878-1879 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Walker, Charles N., 1851 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - War of 1812 - Walker, John-Walton (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Walker, John, 1871-1872 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Wallace, Thomas, 1854 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Waller, Edmund, 1874-1879 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Walsh, William H., 1857 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Walton, R. T., 1880 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - War of 1812 - Wancock-Warner (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Wancock, John, 1852-1853 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Warberton, Benjamin, 1878-1879 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Warberton, Benjamin, 1879-1880 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Warner, Samuel, 1851 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - War of 1812 - Warthen-Watkins, John (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Warthen, James, 1857 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Wash, William H., 1853-1854 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Washer, William, 1851-1854 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Watkins, Francis O., 1851 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Watkins, John, 1854 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - War of 1812 - Watkins, John [R.] (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Watkins, John [R.], 1879-1880 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Watkins, Philip, 1851-1859, 1878 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Watkins, Royal, 1854 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Watson, George, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Watson, Samuel, 1878-1879 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Watson, Simon, 1880-1881 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - War of 1812 - Watt-White, George (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Watt, George, 1851-1855 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Watt, George (oversize), 1851-1855 (Box 34a, Folder 2)
      - Watts, William, 1850 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Webb, Abraham, 1871 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Weisiger, Daniel W., 1857 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Wells, John, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - White, Dabney, 1853-1854 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - White, George, 1879 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - War of 1812 - White, John-White, Warner (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - White, John, 1879-Oct. 1880 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - White, John, Oct. 1880-1882 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - White, John, 1881 (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - White, Nathaniel, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - White, Warner, 1882 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - War of 1812 - White-Wilkinson (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - White, [_], 1882 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Wicker, John, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Wiggins, Asa, 1856 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Wiley, John F., 1853 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Wilkerson, Nicholas, 1880-1881 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Wilkinson, Richard C., 1855, 1878-1879 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - War of 1812 - (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Williams, Archer, 1854-1856 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Williams, Harvey, 1856 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Williams, Henry, 1852-1857 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Williams, James, 1855 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Williams, Thomas, 1878-1879 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - War of 1812 - Williams, Thomas-Wilson (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Williams, Thomas, 1878-1881 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Williams, Thomas, 1881-1882 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Williamson, John, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Wills, Willis C., 1879 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Wilson, Levi, 1858 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - War of 1812 - Winbush-Winfree, Thomas (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Winbush, Epaphaditus, 1853 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Winebrennor, Peter, 1850-1856 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Winfield, Joel, 1856 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Winfree, Mathew, 1852-1856 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Winfree, Peter, 1851-1858 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Winfree, Thomas, 1851 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - War of 1812 - Winfree, Valentine-Wood (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Winfree, Valentine, 1854 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Wood, James, 1879 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Wood, Jeremiah "Jerry," 1876-May 1880 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Wood, Jeremiah "Jerry," June-September 1880 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - War of 1812 - Woodfin-Woodson (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Woodfin, George, 1853-1855 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Woodhouse, H. B., 1873 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Woods, William, 1881 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Woodson, Alexander, 1856 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Woodson, Frederick, 1852, 1857 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Woodson, Joseph, 1857 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Woodson, William, 1879 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - War of 1812 - Woody-Wright (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Woody, James, 1851 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Wray, Anderson, 1855 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Wright, George, 1855-1856 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Wright, John Woodson, 1855 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Wright, James, 1879 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Wright, Joseph, 1880-1882 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Wright, W. A., 1852, 1855 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - War of 1812 - Yarborough-Zigler (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Yarborough, John, 1878-1880 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Yeaman, Pleasant, 1878-1879 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Young, Richard, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Young, William P., 1856 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Zigler, Leonard, 1852 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - War of 1812 - Unidentified and multiple pension applicants, 1817-1850 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1817 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1818 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1819 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1820 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1825 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1831 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1832 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1833 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1838 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1841 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1847 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1848 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1849 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants (oversize), 1814, 1849 (Box 34a, Folder 3)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1849-1850 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - War of 1812 - Unidentified and multiple pension applicants, 1850-1854 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1850-1851 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1852 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1853 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1854 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - War of 1812 - Unidentified and multiple pension applicants, 1855-1857 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1855 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1856 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1857 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - War of 1812 - Unidentified and multiple pension applicants, 1858-1878 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1858 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1860 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1861 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1866 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1869 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1872 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1873 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1876 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1877 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1878 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - War of 1812 - Unidentified and multiple pension applicants, 1879-1882 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1879 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1880 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1881 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Unidentified and multiple applicants, 1882 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - War of 1812 - Unidentified and multiple pension applicants, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 3-5)
  - Mexican War, 1846-1881 and n.d., 0.45 cubic feet. (Boxes 20-21)
    These are pension files, 1846-1881 and n.d., for claimants with military service during the Mexican War.
    - Mexican War - Aiken-Blunhall (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Aiken, Edward A., 1847-1855 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Allis, James, 1857 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Bailey, John W., 1854 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Bailey, Richard, 1854 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Balster, John, 1852 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Barker, John, 1856 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Barker, William, 1847-1854 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Blunhall, Robert W., 1851-1853 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Mexican War - Bottoms-Craft (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Bottoms, Pleasant, 1847 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Bowles, Bernard H., 1881 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Bradley, James, 1856 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Brown, Alexander, 1853, 1857 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Cardona, Miguel, 1855 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Childress, Richard J., 1855 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Clark, John A., 1847-1857 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Craft, George W., 1848 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Mexican War - Curtis-Fortune (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Curtis, William H., 1856-1857 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Ehrenberg, John, 1853 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Enroughty, Jackson, 1851 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Enroughty, John, 1855 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Farris, John, 1854-1856 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Fields, William, 1853 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Fortune, John, 1855 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Mexican War - Godwin-Hooper (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Godwin, John M., 1879 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Harper, Kenton, 1853 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Harris, Hugh N., 1851-1852 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Harrison, John N., 1856 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Hobbs, Alphaus H., 1860 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Hooper, William I., 1866 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Mexican War - Howell-Kimbrough (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Howell, James, 1852 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Jackson, Robert, 1853 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Jefferson, Hezekiah, 1857 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Kendrick, Francis W., 1852-1853 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Kimbrough, William J., n.d. (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Mexican War - Leckie-Patton (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Leckie, John, 1858 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Lefeve, Lewis, 1853-1854 (Box 20, Folder 11)